Last time on Zombieland Saga, after screwing up our first paid job, we got not one, but two more chances to shine.
First, we starred in a commercial for Drive-In Toddy and worked our tail feathers off to try and cluck up some quick butts.
The next step in our quest for press was competing in the Gat-Olympics.
But instead of getting a taste of fame, we just got a mouthful of mud.
Chicken and mud, those must be the ingredients for success!
People are bound to know who we are now!
Uh, why is no one agreeing with me?
Come on, please tell me we'll make it!
Ah, damn it! This is starting to get really frustrating.
How's it possible that none of these girls have social media?
And their website's nothing but photos of their past events?
I kinda like that. It means they don't just follow the trends.
I know you wanted us to track these kids, but there's nothing to track.
After a month, you'd think we'd have something to show for it.
I wonder, who the heck are they?
That's what they are saying.
Who the heck are they?
I wonder, who the heck are they?
Hey, time out!
Uh...
We're still too slow on that last part.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I'll just slow down.
Hmmm...
This new song has a duet that highlights Ai and Junko.
You two will be front and center.
I feel so guilty.
I'm supposed to be on lead vocals, but...
Well, it is fast.
We'll just have to focus on perfecting the most crucial parts of the song.
Okay, I'm gonna run through the whole thing myself to see how it flows.
You guys can take a break.
Something about her.
Hello?
We're out of shampoo.
What's this glowing box?
It's called a computer.
We're going to use it to figure out what kind of idols are big right now.
They come up with the wildest things.
Hey, stop!
You're going to break it.
Oh dear.
My apologies.
Hold on, you guys.
What if Kotoro catches us?
Don't worry.
His nighttime bath should take at least another 20 minutes.
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's my third time doing this.
Hey Ai, do you think Fran Shushu has its own homepage?
I do, and I am not going back to it.
But why not?
You'll die from cringing.
Huh?
Uh, die again, I mean.
Hello?
Uh...
Anyway, I've been doing a lot of digging around lately.
So much has changed since my day, especially for idols.
Lots of popular groups who seem like they would stay together forever already broke up.
Public interest in idols does fluctuate.
Wait, what's that mean for us though?
Even if idols aren't in right now, we'll still try our best.
Okay?
Um, yeah, okay.
Alright.
Who's doing events?
Let me see.
This new technology is so useful.
Just look at them all.
Cool.
Let's start with the ones that seem interesting.
Oh, what's Saga Rock?
That sounds like fun.
Sure does.
Do you like rock?
Yep.
We all know Mentai Rock is huge in Kyushu.
Mentai what?
Haha!
I'll kill you.
But I seriously don't know.
It says here it's the largest outdoor rock event on the island of Kyushu.
No way!
We gotta get in on that!
Looks like it'd be easy to get on one of the big stages, but…
It must be amazing to perform at a place like that with so many people!
I've done a lot of press appearances, so I won't even be that nervous!
Yeah, let's go for it!
If we put in enough practice, we'll bring the house down!
It's not that easy though.
Huh?
You have no idea.
The venue's huge.
A lot of work goes into performing somewhere like that.
Oh, right.
It would be better for us to take small steps than dive headfirst into the deep end.
Sorry.
I understand you.
But we don't really have the time to gradually build our popularity.
We need to find a way to get our name out there quick.
Take the group I was in before this.
We played for audiences in the tens of thousands after just a year on the scene.
One year?
How did you attract so many people?
If you're trying to be perfect from the beginning, then you'll never get anywhere.
Fans like to see you improve over time and feel like they're a part of it.
Like it's a journey.
I don't know…
And obviously, we still need to try our best every step of the way.
It's the first time to be perfect.
Hey look!
Isn't that your old group I?
Which one?
Right there!
You see?
They'll be at Sokka Rock!
Iron frill?
Sweet!
Oh, good day to you!
Dear friend!
Shushu!
I have come to bring you good tidings!
I am the great-
That's enough!
Just spit it out!
All right.
I'm delighted to say that I've got some excellent news for you all.
Does anybody want to guess?
You have some fans now!
Thanks to the chicken ad, followed by the Gatalympics coverage, you've gained a bit
of traction online.
Wow!
Really?
What'd I say?
Can't get any better than Drive-In Toddy!
No matter how stupid we look, I guess there's no such thing as bad press.
What are you talking about?
Even when you're covered in mud, Franz Shushu always finds a way to sparkle!
Drive-In Toddy!
Huh?
You're close!
Let me show you how!
It's like this!
To-ring!
Oh, okay!
I think I get it now!
To-ring!
That's not really it either!
Right!
One more!
To-ring!
Are you even watching-
Who the hell cares?!
Why would I need to master your stupid dance routine?!
Don't you look down your nose at me, Pinocchio!
I own you, remember?!
What, Pinocchio?!
You're not a real boy yet!
Now that I've made that crystal clear, here's your new mission.
You're all about to spend a little quality time with the fans of Franz Shushu.
Short notice, as always.
I already announced it on our homepage.
When you say quality time...
For now, I think we'll start with a photo op!
Wait a minute.
What is he talking about?
Oh, I guess what he means is, the fans will take pictures of us, but not with film.
They'll probably just be digital.
Digital?
Uh, how do I explain?
You don't have to wait for the pictures.
Oh, like a Polaroid, right?
Mmm...
I see, we're taking glamour shots with Polaroids!
No, it's not gonna be a big formal thing.
Actually, it will be.
Whoa, for real?!
Usually there's a mini-concert and some merch sales, then pics.
Merch sales, huh?
We have some t-shirts, but no one wants to wear those tacky things.
You must be confused.
Are you keeping up?
I'm fine.
I've found that getting confused doesn't help much.
I'll just relax and take things as they come.
And after this, I've got an even bigger pan on the fire!
So don't let me down, or you might get cut!
That's it, and we are...
From Choo Choo!
Thanks for all your support!
Yeah!
Good morning!
People really showed up!
I can't believe we actually have fans now!
And, uh, if you want, we're gonna have a photo op right after this!
Aw, man.
That's crazy!
You all came here to see us!
I mean...
You guys rock!
It's Coco, dammit!
Ohhhh...
It looks so good!
Ahhhh...
It looks so gross!
Uhhhh...
She's warm!
They're warm!
We have the official Fraun Machu-choo T-shirts available…
...as well as these cute hand towels!
these cute hand towels.
Anyone who buys at least one item
will be eligible for the photo session.
When did we have time to get this stuff made?
Yeah, and what's with that weird design?
All right, everyone, it's time
to get those photo sessions rolling.
We'll start with the lines for number zero and number one,
then we'll get number two and number three.
Photo sessions?
With who?
The fans are lined up to take individual photos with us.
What else would this be?
Huh?
Ready!
Here we go, smile!
What was that?
Okay, next we'll do photographs for numbers four, five, and six.
Number four, it's your turn.
We'll be using this folding screen.
I can't.
Huh?
I'm not posing for pictures.
But why not?
Hurry up, they're waiting.
No!
But you've got the longest line.
You have to.
Idols are supposed to dazzle people from up on stage.
How does this have anything to do with that?
What's wrong?
What the hell was that?
I'm so disappointed in you.
What's wrong?
Oh.
What the hell was that?
I'm so disappointed in you.
Do you want to know how disappointed I am?
Well, if I had to give you a metaphor, it's like...
Stop zombies!
God!
You do understand that this whole thing was your fault, right, Junko?
Walking out on a job doesn't affect just you.
It hurts all of us.
So that's part of our job?
Of course.
But it's so personal.
I don't want to do that.
Listen to me.
Idols do this.
We have fans and they love us.
So they need to feel like we're within reach.
But that's just it.
Besides, you bragged about going big after your first year.
Just from fan events?
Is that more important than being a great performer?
Wait a sec.
Don't put words in my mouth.
You better back off.
Guys, take a chill pill.
She's right.
Relax.
I just think we need to decide what our relationship with fans should be.
You're the only one here who doesn't get it.
Oh my god, what do I do?
I agree that we need our fans.
But we have different opinions about the role they should play.
A good performer doesn't have to depend on them.
No.
But being above your fans is so less century.
You aren't exactly fresh blood yourself.
Don't fight!
If you want to be in a real idol group, then you're going to have to leave your fear behind.
That was uncalled for.
Hey!
Damn it.
That's employment.
Come on!
I'm not going to be history yet.
Come on, Ai.
Can't you two bury the hatchet already?
Just shake hands and admit you were both wrong.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I'm sorry, you guys, but I don't feel like I should go back on anything I said.
Just because each side has a valid point doesn't mean the disagreement can't be resolved.
I thought the rest of you were serious about becoming idols.
We just want you and Junko to stay friends.
But we're not friends.
We work together.
You were in show business, Lily.
You should understand that.
Jeez, you don't have to make her cry.
Don't you walk away from me!
I wouldn't worry.
Things will settle down soon.
Won't they, leader?
What a freaking pain!
Come on, hurry!
I told you, I didn't bring a swimsuit.
I'll get it!
Oh, it's you!
I see.
So you're from a generation earlier than me, huh?
It's more like two.
I would have been an old lady by now.
I was just thinking, I've never really had the chance to ask you what kind of idol you used to be.
Back in those days, it just wasn't the norm for idols to have that kind of fan interaction.
Maybe a meet and greet once in a while, but that's all.
So, no matter where we were, on the stage or the tube, there was always a clear boundary.
Hmm?
Um, wait, what about a tube?
I'm lost.
It's an idol's job to give people something to aspire to.
I could never let the fans get close enough to see my flaws.
Or at least, that's the way it was for the idols I knew.
Just like I'd grown up admiring them, I wanted to become a role model for others, too.
That's why I worked hard, day in and day out.
I was starting to feel like I'd accomplished that.
And I thought maybe, I could keep on doing it.
But on my way to Saga for my first touring Kyushu...
Hmm.
And that was that.
Oh, Junko.
Not just anyone can be an idol.
The same goes for being a zombie.
And if my approach is holding the team back...
I'm sorry, but I can't be in Franshushu.
I just don't belong.
Hmm.
I...
Found you.
Tell me what's wrong.
Hey!
Well, this is messed up.
You look like a wet cat.
Guess we both do.
You know, if I'm being honest, I don't get all this stuff about being idols and having fans.
But I do know you need guts and good backup.
That's all we've got.
I'm surprised.
You're really scared of lightning?
That's because it's how I died.
Damn, what a way to go.
Talk about legendary.
That's not the kind of legend I want to be.
My story isn't over.
I'm still here.
I'm not history yet.
I don't care if I'm a zombie.
I'm gonna get back on stage again.
And then I'll...
You've always been a firecracker, huh?
Saki.
You're still awake?
Yeah, I had trouble sleeping.
Those two.
If this was my old gang, I'd beat both their asses.
Or maybe worse.
Please don't hurt them.
I won't.
But for real, we won't get anywhere if they keep that up.
They need a wake-up call.
The sooner we can fix this, the better.
Yeah.
Good morning, ladies!
Please?
Look!
I've got great news, so pay attention, please!
Anybody want to guess what?
Fine, I'll tell you!
We're on the newcomer's roster for this year's Saga Rock!
Yes, you may applaud me.
The Saga Rock?
You're kidding me.
This is a once-in-an-after-lifetime chance!
And that means...
You girls better not screw it up.
For one day, Saga will be the center of the music world,
and you need to stand at the center of Saga!
This is Franz Shushu's first outdoor show!
Your music will light up the sky and shake the earth!
Thank you!
And we'll see you on the next one!
Bye!
Junko here. If I'm gonna be in everybody's way, I might as well turn into a big stupid mushroom.
Next time on Zombieland Saga, Episode 7. But it's Zombie Mental Saga. I'll go away now.